

CONTACT

- jason.lau971114@gmail.com
- in www.linkedin.com/in/jasonlau1114
- jason-lau.vercel.app
- 還 github.com/fantasy1114

SKILL

Python/Flask/Django

JavaScript/TypeScript

React/Next

Vue/Nuxt

Angular

PHP/Laravel/Symfony

Shopify/Wordpress/Magento

Node/Nest

SQL/NoSQL

Web3

Golang

JASON **LAU**

ABOUT ME

Senior Software Developer with 7+ Years of Experience.

Experienced with numerous software technologies focusing on web and blockchain development.

Got prize in ACM which is part of ICPC when I was a college student.

Led development of \$150K research project which was deemed a "silver standard" by the client. Increased client's revenue 2-fold after fine-tuning AI/ML-based algorithms.

Provide high-quality code and power communication.

Eager to support building an impeccable online reputation by providing high-level customer support for start-ups and firms.

Worked on flexible projects for unlimited clients around the world.

Strong at building architecture of backend systems and have good sensitive in frontend developing .

Specialist at Test Driven Development.

EXPERIENCE

SENIOR FULL STACK DEVELOPER

Feb 2021-Present upwork, Freelancer

- Strategic and management consulting for blockchain and cryptocurrency, from ICOs to capital raises to systems design.
- Backend development using Python/Django integrated Unit testing for backend system and used to deploy server to digital ocean using Docker.
- Integrated Django CMS using wagtail to build page more easily and more fantastic.
- Built and launched Smart Contracts for Genesis NFT, Pod and Marketplace as well. Prefer to use ERC-721 based NFT rather than ERC-1155.
- Supported the DevOps team to automate CI/CD processes
- Worked with Core Java to develop automated solutions to include web interfaces using HTML, CSS, JavaScript and Web services
- Implemented complex UI components with React / Vue / TypeScript and SCSS
- Developed pages routing capabilities for bookmarking, filters, validations and React components such as grid, buttons, carousels, date pickers, modal dialogs and other input components

SENIOR FULL STACK DEVELOPER

Feb 2017 - Jan 2021 Ratio Finance, United States

- Slashed payroll/benefits administration costs 30% by negotiating pricing and fees, while ensuring the continuation and enhancements of services.
- Utilize Python/Django, PostgreSQL to implement scalable Full Stack Software solutions.
- Participate in the full lifecycle of development for company web application using Django.
- Integrated Auth0 login and SendGrid API to send mail to users.
- Created restful APIs using Laravel and consumed them with React.js.
- Configured Google analytics module for tracking the visitors for the website.
- Strong programming experience in Laravel with sufficient exposure to Windows and Linux.
- Fixed bugs and implemented TDD for both Frontend and Backend.
- Developed Responsive Websites that could be served by desktop, Tablets and mobile devices using React.js.
- Integrated payment system for product checkout using Authorize, payment API.

Rust

Solidity

CI / CD

AWS

Docker

LANGUANGE



COURSE

- Solidity Smart Contracts:
 Build DApps in Ethereum Blockchain
 Get Certificate, Udemy
 July 2018 Aug 2019
- Ethereum and Solidity: The Developer's complete guide, Udemy Feb 2018 – June 2018

HOBBIES

- Skiing
- Volleyball
- Table Tennis
- Basketball

- Worked with JEST unit test framework to write unit tests for JavaScript code.
- Worked closely with the back-end team to display data using the Custom Components, library components, Redux, Redux-Saga.
- Worked with backend engineers to optimize existing API calls to create efficiencies by deprecating unneeded API calls

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

Nov 2015 - Feb 2017 Mezurashico, Japan

- Developed an E-commerce platform using React for frontend and NodeJS for backend.
- Developed Responsive Websites that could be served by desktop, Tablets and mobile devices using React.js.
- Integrated payment system for product checkout using Authorize, payment API.
- Worked with JEST unit test framework to write unit tests for JavaScript code.
- Worked closely with the back-end team to display data using the Custom Components, library components, Redux, Redux-Saga.
- Worked with backend engineers to optimize existing API calls to create efficiencies by deprecating unneeded API calls.
- \bullet Involved in all agile ceremonies like Daily stand-ups, Backlog pointing sessions, Planning sessions, retrospection, etc.
- Implemented various screens for the frontend using React.js and used various predefined components from NPM(Node Package Manager) and redux library.
- \bullet Interacted with the Testing Team, Scrum Masters and Business Analysts to fix issues.

EDUCATION

KEIO UNIVERSITY, JAPAN

May 2012 - Sep 2015

- Bachelor of Science (BS).
- $\bullet \ \ \text{Get Third place at ACM, part of International College Programming Contest} (ICPC)$

PROJECTS

- https://www.offers.jp Job Platform
- https://www.getflair.io Generation Marketing
- https://cropper.finance Decentralized Ecosystem
- https://shmacked.com
 Delivering system(Snacks, drinks, nicotine and alcohol)
- https://perfectyourtrading.com Crypto Trading Education
- https://www.fazwaz.com The Biggest Real Estate Marketplace of Thailand
- https://www.bobbytariq.com Advanced Learning Management System
- https://nftcars.me NFT Game site.